Luther-Bagby collection, Inclusive: 1821-2001, Bulk: 1890-1970
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Bagby Papers, 1843-1993; 2; 17 document boxes and 2 oversized boxes and 2 oversized folders.
  - Correspondence, 1868-1993; 1
    - To William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby from Alice Bagby, 1917-1919 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - To William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby from Alice Bagby, 1919-1920 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - To William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby from Alice Bagby, 1920-1922 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - To William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby from Alice Bagby Smith, 1922-1935 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - To William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby from Alice Bagby Smith, 1922-1926, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - To William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby from Alice Bagby Smith, 1935-1937, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - To William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby from Alice Bagby Smith, 1940-1942 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - To Anne Luther Bagby from Alice Bagby, 1903-1907 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - To Anne Luther Bagby from Alice Bagby, 1910-1911 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - To Anne Luther Bagby from Alice Bagby: (1 of 2), 1914-1917 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - To Anne Luther Bagby from Alice Bagby: (2 of 2), 1914-1917 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - To Anne Luther Bagby from Taylor Crawford Bagby, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Ermine Bagby, 1881, 1883, 1889 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - To William Buck Bagby from Helen Bagby, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - To Anne Luther Bagby from Grace Gooda; to Grace Gooda from Helen Bagby, 1919, 925 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - To Anne Luther Bagby from Zollie Luther: (1 of 2), 1880-1888, 1890-1892; 1912; 1914 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - To Anne Luther Bagby from Zollie Luther: (2 of 2), 1880-1888, 1890-1892; 1912; 1914 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - To Anne Luther Bagby from Helen Frances Smith, Thelma Lou Smith, and Paul Bagby Smith, 1940-1942 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - To William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1883-1907 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - To William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1914-1939 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1912-1913 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1914-1916 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (1 of 2), 1916 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (2 of 2), 1916 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1917-1918 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1917-1919 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (1 of 4), 1920 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (2 of 4), 1920 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (3 of 4), 1920 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (4 of 4), 1920 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1921 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1922-1923 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (1 of 3), 1924 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (2 of 3), 1924 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (3 of 3), 1924 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1925-1927 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1929-1931 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - To and from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1931-1934 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby to family, 1868-1871, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby to family, 1881 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby to family: (1 of 2), 1881-1882 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby to family: (2 of 2), 1881-1882 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby to family, 1882-1884 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby to family, 1883-1885 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby to family, 1883-1891 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby to family, 1891-1907 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby to family, 1908-1913 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby to family, 1879-1881 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby to family, 1910-1911 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby to family, 1911-1913 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby, Anne Luther Bagby, and Taylor Crawford Bagby to family, 1914-1915 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Outgoing from William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby to family, 1915-1917 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - To Alice Bagby from Anne Luther Bagby and William Buck Bagby, 1901, 1914-1915 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - To Alice Bagby from Anne Luther Bagby and William Buck Bagby: (1 of 2), 1915 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - To Alice Bagby from Anne Luther Bagby and William Buck Bagby: (2 of 2), 1915 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - To Alice Bagby from Anne Luther Bagby and William Buck Bagby: (1 of 2), 1916 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - To Alice Bagby from Anne Luther Bagby and William Buck Bagby: (2 of 2), 1916 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - To Alice Bagby from Anne Luther Bagby and William Buck Bagby, 1916-1917 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - To Alice Bagby from Anne Luther Bagby and William Buck Bagby, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - To Alice Bagby from Anne Luther Bagby and William Buck Bagby, 1917-1918 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - To Alice Bagby from Anne Luther Bagby and William Buck Bagby, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - To Alice Bagby from Anne Luther Bagby and William Buck Bagby, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - To Alice Bagby from Anne Luther Bagby and William Buck Bagby: (1 of 2), 1920 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - To Alice Bagby from Anne Luther Bagby and William Buck Bagby: (2 of 2), 1920 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - To Alice Bagby from Anne Luther Bagby and William Buck Bagby, 1921, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - To Alice Bagby from Harley Smith, 1920-1921 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - To Alice Bagby from Harley Smith: (1 of 4), 1921 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - To Alice Bagby from Harley Smith: (2 of 4), 1921 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - To Alice Bagby from Harley Smith: (3 of 4), 1921 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - To Alice Bagby from Harley Smith: (4 of 4), 1921 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - To Alice Bagby from Harley Smith, 1921-1922 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - To Alice Bagby from Harley Smith: (1 of 3), 1922 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - To Alice Bagby from Harley Smith: (2 of 3), 1922 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - To Alice Bagby from Harley Smith: (3 of 3), 1922 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - To Alice Bagby from Oliver Bagby, 1912-1916 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - To Alice Bagby from Oliver Bagby, 1916-1917 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - To Alice Bagby from Oliver Bagby: (1 of 2), 1917 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - To Alice Bagby from Oliver Bagby: (2 of 2), 1917 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - To Alice Bagby from Oliver Bagby: (1 of 5), 1918 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - To Alice Bagby from Oliver Bagby: (2 of 5), 1918 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - To Alice Bagby from Oliver Bagby: (3 of 5), 1918 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - To Alice Bagby from Oliver Bagby: (4 of 5), 1918 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - To Alice Bagby from Oliver Bagby: (5 of 5), 1918 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - To Alice Bagby from Helen Edna Bagby, 1907, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - To Alice Bagby from Helen Edna Bagby, 1914-1918 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - To Alice Bagby from Helen Edna Bagby, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - To Alice Bagby from Helen Edna Bagby, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - To Alice Bagby from Helen Edna Bagby, 1921-1935 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - To Alice Bagby from Ermine Bagby Sowell, 1915-1920 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - To Alice Bagby from Ermine Bagby Sowell, 1920-1922, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - To Alice Bagby from Sydney Sowell, Anne Sowell, and Maurice Sowell, 1919-1921 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - To Alice Bagby from Albert Ian Bagby, 1915-1920 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - To Alice Bagby from Taylor Crawford Bagby and Frances Bagby, 1916-1921 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - To Alice Bagby, 1908-1913 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - To Alice Bagby, 1918-1920 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - To Alice Bagby: (1 of 2), 1920 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - To Alice Bagby: (2 of 2), 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - To and from Alice Bagby, 1918 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Sowell, Margrett, 1891-1937 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Willson Bagby (1 of 3), 1908-1912 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Willson Bagby (2 of 3), 1908-1912 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Willson Bagby (3 of 3), 1908-1912 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Leecy, 1963-1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - To and from Tia, 1948-1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - To and from Tia, 1974-1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - To and from Tia, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - To and from Albert Ian and Thelma Frith Bagby (1 of 2), 1945-1955 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - To and from Albert Ian and Thelma Frith Bagby (2 of 2), 1945-1955 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - To and from Albert Ian and Thelma Frith Bagby, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - To and from Albert Ian and Thelma Frith Bagby (1 of 2), 1961-1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - To and from Albert Ian and Thelma Frith Bagby (2 of 2), 1961-1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - To Zollie Luther Jones from Ermine Bagby, 1899 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - To Ermine Bagby from Anne Jaudon Luther, Zollie Luther, and Anne Luther Bagby, 1888, 1904 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - To Taylor Crawford Bagby, Alice Bagby, and Oliver Bagby, 1907, 1910-1911; 1917 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - To Nellie Buck from Ermine Bagby Sowell and Anne Margarett, 1937, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - From Oliver Bagby, 1913 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - From Helen Bagby Harrison, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - To and from Helen Bagby Harrison, 1935-1955 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - From William Coleman Harrison to family, 1925-1926 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - From William Coleman Harrison to family, 1926-1927 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - From William Coleman Harrison to family, 1927-1929 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - From William Coleman Harrison to family, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - To William Coleman Harrison, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - To William Coleman Harrison, 1959-1967 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - William Coleman Harrison: Biography, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Regarding William Coleman Harrison, 1971, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Literary Productions, 1843-1989; 2
    This subseries includes several manuscripts of Bagbys of Brazil, by Helen Bagby Harrison. The manuscript number was assigned by the creator and has been maintained in the folder title. This series also includes journals, school papers, and other literary productions created by the Bagby family.
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #1: (1 of 6), 1927 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #1: (2 of 6), 1927 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #1: (3 of 6), 1927 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #1: (4 of 6), 1927 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #1: (5 of 6), 1927 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #1: (6 of 6), 1927 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #2: (1 of 4), 1935 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #2: (2 of 4), 1935 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #2: (3 of 4), 1935 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #2: (4 of 4), 1935 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #4: (1 of 10), 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #4: (2 of 10), 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #4: (3 of 10), 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #4: (4 of 10), 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #4: (5 of 10), 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #4: (6 of 10), 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #4: (7 of 10), 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #4: (8 of 10), 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #4: (9 of 10), 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #4: (10 of 10), 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (1 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (2 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (3 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (4 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (5 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (6 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (7 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (8 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (9 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (10 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (11 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (12 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (13 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (14 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5: (15 of 15), 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #5, undated (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (1 of 16), 1945 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (2 of 16), 1945 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (3 of 16), 1945 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (4 of 16), 1945 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (5 of 16), 1945 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (6 of 16), 1945 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (7 of 16), 1945 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (8 of 16), 1945 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (9 of 16), 1945 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (10 of 16), 1945 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (11 of 16), 1945 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (12 of 16), 1945 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (13 of 16), 1945 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (14 of 16), 1945 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (15 of 16), 1945 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #6: (16 of 16), 1945 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #8: (1 of 5), 1953 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #8: (2 of 5), 1953 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #8: (3 of 5), 1953 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #8: (4 of 5), 1953 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Manuscript #8: (5 of 5), 1953 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Portuguese Manuscript: (1 of 7), undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Portuguese Manuscript: (2 of 7), undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Portuguese Manuscript: (3 of 7), undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Portuguese Manuscript: (4 of 7), undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Portuguese Manuscript: (5 of 7), undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Portuguese Manuscript: (6 of 7), undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Portuguese Manuscript: (7 of 7), undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Corrections and Correspondence: (1 of 8), 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Corrections and Correspondence: (2 of 8), 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Corrections and Correspondence: (3 of 8), 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Corrections and Correspondence: (4 of 8), 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Corrections and Correspondence: (5 of 8), 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Corrections and Correspondence: (6 of 8), 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Corrections and Correspondence: (7 of 8), 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Manuscripts: Bagbys of Brazil: Corrections and Correspondence: (8 of 8), 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Family Histories: Biographical Material, 1843; 1920-1939 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Family Histories: Biographical Material, 1931-1945 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Family Histories: Biographical Material, 1984-1987, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Family Histories: Biographical Material, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Family Histories: Certificates and Diplomas, 1880-1920, undated (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Family Histories: Certificates and Diplomas, 1918-1920 (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Family Histories: Notes, Clippings, and Correspondence: William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1880-1945 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Family Histories: Notes, Clippings, and Correspondence: William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby, 1884-1937 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Family Histories: Notes, Clippings, and Correspondence, 1881-1968, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Family Histories: Notes, Clippings, and Correspondence, 1959; 1982; 1985 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Family Histories: Notes, Clippings, and Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Family Histories: Notes, Clippings, and Correspondence: (1 of 5), undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Family Histories: Notes, Clippings, and Correspondence: (2 of 5), undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Family Histories: Notes, Clippings, and Correspondence: (3 of 5), undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Family Histories: Notes, Clippings, and Correspondence: (4 of 5), undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Family Histories: Notes, Clippings, and Correspondence: (5 of 5), undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Family Histories: Illness and death of Anne Luther Bagby: (1 of 4), 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Family Histories: Illness and death of Anne Luther Bagby: (2 of 4), 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Family Histories: Illness and death of Anne Luther Bagby: (3 of 4), 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Family Histories: Illness and death of Anne Luther Bagby: (4 of 4), 1942-1943 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Diaries: Anne Luther Bagby, 1881 January-April (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Diaries: Alice Bagby: General, 1914 November-1915 August (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Diaries: Alice Bagby: Booklist, 1915-1936 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Diaries: William Coleman Harrison: General, 1932-1933 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Diaries: William Coleman Harrison: General, 1935-1936 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Diaries: Helen Bagby Harrison: Prayer Journal, circa 1959-1965 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Diaries: William Buck Bagby: Financial Diary and Date Book, 1935-1940 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Diaries: Notes of William Buck Bagby, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Diaries: Notes of Anne Luther Bagby, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Essays: Published Writings: William Buck Bagby, 1881; 1889; 1899; 1913; 1939 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Essays: Published Writings: William Buck Bagby, 1927, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Essays: Published Writings: Anne Luther Bagby, 1884; 1886; 1942, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Essays: Published Writings: Anne Luther Bagby, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Essays: "Students Follow Paths to Missionary Fields", 1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Essays: "Aunt Helen Bagby Harrison", 1989 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Essays: Poetry, Prayers, and Sayings: English: (1 of 4), undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Essays: Poetry, Prayers, and Sayings: English: (2 of 4), undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Essays: Poetry, Prayers, and Sayings: English: (3 of 4), undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Essays: Poetry, Prayers, and Sayings: English: (4 of 4), undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Essays: Poetry, Prayers, and Sayings: Portuguese: (1 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Essays: Poetry, Prayers, and Sayings: Portuguese: (2 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Church and Class Participation Lists, 1927-1936 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Church and Class Participation Lists, 1928-1932, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Church and Class Participation Lists, 1930-1934, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Church and Class Participation Lists, 1941-1954, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Church and Class Participation Lists, 1954-1961 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Church and Class Participation Lists, 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Church and Class Participation Lists, 1965-1972 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Church and Class Participation Lists, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Portuguese Curriculum: (1 of 3), undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Portuguese Curriculum: (2 of 3), undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Portuguese Curriculum: (3 of 3), undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Alice Bagby School Papers: Southwestern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Alice Bagby School Papers: Baylor Female College [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor], undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Alice Bagby School Papers: General: (1 of 2), 1918-1921 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Alice Bagby School Papers: General: (2 of 2), 1918-1921 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Alice Bagby School Papers: General: (1 of 4), undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Alice Bagby School Papers: General: (2 of 4), undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Alice Bagby School Papers: General: (3 of 4), undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Alice Bagby School Papers: General: (4 of 4), undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Songs: Texas, 1936, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Songs: Brazil, 1960, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Books: The Baptist Hymn Book, by William C. Buck, 1842 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Books: Our Baylor, by E. C. Moore, 1895 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Books: Sacred Songs and Solos, compiled by Ira D. Sankey, 1910 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Books: Baptizo-Dip-Only, by W. A. Jarrel, 1910; 1913 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Books: Boston Chamber of Commerce South American Tour, by Albert Leonard Squier, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Books: These Gracious Years, by George W. Truett, 1929-1930 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Books: Seed Sower in Brazil, by Josephine Taylor Watts, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Books: Os Bagby do Brasil, by Helen Bagby Harrison, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 4)